function e(e){return e&&e.__esModule?e.default:e}var n;n=JSON.parse('[{"id":1,"question":"What is the keyword for determine the constant value at Javascript ?","answer1":"let","answer2":"var","answer3":"object","answer4":"const","correctAnswer":"answer4"},{"id":2,"question":"In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error ?","answer1":"Syntax error","answer2":"Missing of semicolons","answer3":"Division by zero","answer4":"Missing of bracket","correctAnswer":"answer2"},{"id":3,"question":"Which of the following function of the String object returns the character in the string starting at the specified position via the specified number of characters ?","answer1":"slice()","answer2":"split()","answer3":"substr()","answer4":"search()","correctAnswer":"answer3"},{"id":4,"question":"In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that :","answer1":"Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.","answer2":"Both are x and y are equal in value only.","answer3":"Both are equal in the value and data type.","answer4":"Both are not same at all.","correctAnswer":"answer3"},{"id":4,"question":"In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that :","answer1":"Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.","answer2":"Both are x and y are equal in value only.","answer3":"Both are equal in the value and data type.","answer4":"Both are not same at all.","correctAnswer":"answer3"},{"id":5,"question":"Which one of the following is an ternary operator ? ","answer1":"?","answer2":":","answer3":"-","answer4":"+","correctAnswer":"answer1"},{"id":6,"question":"\'An expression that can legally appear on the left side of an assignment expression.\' is a well known explanation for variables, properties of objects, and elements of arrays. They are called : ","answer1":"Properties","answer2":"Prototypes","answer3":"Definition","answer4":"Lvalue","correctAnswer":"answer4"},{"id":7,"question":"In a case, where the value of the operator is NULL , the typeof returned by the unary operator is called : ","answer1":"object","answer2":"string","answer3":"boolean","answer4":"undefined","correctAnswer":"answer1"},{"id":8,"question":"A collection of elements of the same data type which may either in order or not, is called : ","answer1":"String","answer2":"Array","answer3":"Serialized Object","answer4":"Object","correctAnswer":"answer2"},{"id":9,"question":"Which one of the following keywords is used for defining the function in the JavaScript ?","answer1":"Void","answer2":"init","answer3":"main","answer4":"function","correctAnswer":"answer4"},{"id":10,"question":"Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript ?","answer1":"getElementById","answer2":"getElementsByClassName()","answer3":"Both A and B","answer4":"None of the above","correctAnswer":"answer3"}]');const t=localStorage.getItem("answeredQuestions")?JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("answeredQuestions")):[];let r=null;const s=e=>{const n=document.getElementById(e);n.classList.add("invisible"),n.classList.remove("visible")},a=()=>e(n),o=e=>{localStorage.setItem("currentQuestion",JSON.stringify({id:e.id,question:e.question,answer1:e.answer1,answer2:e.answer2,answer3:e.answer3,answer4:e.answer4}))},i=()=>JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("currentQuestion")),c=e=>{t.push({id:e.id,question:e.question,answer1:e.answer1,answer2:e.answer2,answer3:e.answer3,answer4:e.answer4,isCorrect:e.isCorrect}),localStorage.setItem("answeredQuestions",JSON.stringify(t))},l=e=>{(e=>{const n=document.getElementById(e);n.classList.add("visible"),n.classList.remove("invisible")})("verifyAnswerModal"),(e=>{r=e})(e)},w=()=>{a().find((e=>e.id===i().id)).correctAnswer===r?(c({...i(),isCorrect:!0}),a()[a().length-1].id!==i().id?(o(a().find((e=>e.id===i().id+1))),window.location.href="./questions.html"):d()):(c({...i(),isCorrect:!1}),a()[a().length-1].id!==i().id?(o(a().find((e=>e.id===i().id+1))),window.location.href="./questions.html"):d())},d=()=>{const e=t.filter((e=>!0===e.isCorrect)).length,n=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("user"));n.score=e,localStorage.setItem("user",JSON.stringify(n)),window.location.href="./scoreboard.html"};document.querySelector("#verifyAnswerModal .close-button").addEventListener("click",(()=>s("verifyAnswerModal"))),document.querySelectorAll(".verifyAnswerModal-buttons button")[0].addEventListener("click",(()=>w())),document.querySelectorAll(".verifyAnswerModal-buttons button")[1].addEventListener("click",(()=>s("verifyAnswerModal"))),document.getElementById("quitGameButton").addEventListener("click",(()=>{localStorage.removeItem("user"),window.location.href="./index.html"}));const u=document.querySelector("#questions-area h3"),h=document.querySelector("#answerButton1"),f=document.querySelector("#answerButton2"),m=document.querySelector("#answerButton3"),y=document.querySelector("#answerButton4");h.addEventListener("click",(e=>l(e.target.id.replace("Button","")))),f.addEventListener("click",(e=>l(e.target.id.replace("Button","")))),m.addEventListener("click",(e=>l(e.target.id.replace("Button","")))),y.addEventListener("click",(e=>l(e.target.id.replace("Button",""))));let g=i();if(g&&1!==g.id)u.innerText=g.question,h.innerText=g.answer1,f.innerText=g.answer2,m.innerText=g.answer3,y.innerText=g.answer4;else{const e=a()[0];o(e),u.innerText=e.question,h.innerText=e.answer1,f.innerText=e.answer2,m.innerText=e.answer3,y.innerText=e.answer4,document.title=`Question ${e.id}`}
//# sourceMappingURL=questions.503cdac9.js.map
